Guide to the ACT UP New York records, 1969, 1982-1997 [bulk 1987-1995]
The New York Public Library. Manuscripts and Archives Division.
- Series X. Published and near-print materials, 1969, 1982-1995, n.d; 557278; 58 boxes
  - X.C. Near-print materials and assorted publications, 1982-1995, n.d.; 557339; 14 boxes
    - AIDS Research and Human Retroviruses 3.2, 1987; 557341; This issue was sponsored by the Burroughs Wellcome Company. (Reel 135, Box 164, Folder 2)
    - AIDS Research in the Netherlands, 1992; 557342 (Reel 135, Box 164, Folder 3)
    - AIDS Treatment Registry, 1990; 557343 (Reel 135, Box 164, Folder 4)
    - American Foundation for AIDS Research (AmFAR), National Institute of Allergy and Infectious Diseases (U.S.), and Pharmaceutical Manufacturers Association. AIDS/HIV Experimental Treatment Directory. Vol. 3, No. 1. New York: The Foundation, 1989 May; 557344; Not microfilmed (Box 164, Folder 5)
    - American Medical Association (AMA). "AIDS Victims at Risk for Rare Bacterial Infection", 1982 Dec 10; 557345; Press release (Reel 135, Box 164, Folder 6)
    - Bass, Susan. Entitlements. Outposted HIV Counselor Program, circa 1989; 557346 (Reel 135, Box 164, Folder 7)
    - Benefits Source Book, 1992; 557347 (Reel 135, Box 164, Folder 8)
    - Biggar, Robert J., et al. Seroepidemiology of HTLV-III Antibodies in a Remote Population of Eastern Zaire, 1985; 557348 (Reel 135, Box 164, Folder 9)
    - Bloom, Barry R. Hearing on Tuberculosis: Hearing Before the Human Resources and Intergovernmental Relations Subcommittee, 1992; 557349 (Reel 135, Box 164, Folder 10)
    - British National Formulary 21, Mar 1991; 557350 (Reel 135, Box 164, Folder 11)
    - Bronx AIDS Resource Directory, 1992; 557351 (Reel 144, Box 176, Folder 1)
    - Brussell, Mae, et al. AIDS/Germ War Update, 1987; 557352 (Reel 135, Box 164, Folder 12)
    - California, 557353
      - City and County of San Francisco, California. Women and Infants at Risk for HIV Infection: Guidelines and Protocols for Prevention and Care, 1987-1989; 557354 (Reel 136, Box 165, Folder 1)
      - Southern California HIV Treatment Directory, 1990; 557355 (Reel 136, Box 165, Folder 2)
    - Carter, George M. Notes from the HIV Community Forum. Toronto, Ontario, 1993; 557356 (Reel 136, Box 165, Folder 3)
    - Commission of the European Communities. AIDS Research within the Biomedical and Health Research Programme, 1987-1991; 557357 (Reel 136, Box 165, Folder 4)
    - Compendium of Organizations with International AIDS Programmes, Part I, 557358 (Reel 136, Box 165, Folder 5)
    - Delaney, Martin. The Manhattan Project of 1943, the War on Cancer, and AIDS Research, 557359 (Reel 136, Box 165, Folder 6)
    - Democratic Study Group. Special Report on AIDS Legislative Issues, 1987; 557360 (Reel 136, Box 165, Folder 7)
    - Drop-In Center for Drug Addicted Prostitutes, Foundation for Research on Sexually Transmitted Diseases, Inc. Project Summary, 557361 (Reel 136, Box 165, Folder 8)
    - Elswood. Important New T4 Cell Discovery in AIDS, 1989; 557362 (Reel 136, Box 165, Folder 9)
    - Executive Intelligence Review. An Emergency War Plan to Fight AIDS and Other Pandemics, 1986; 557363; Not microfilmed (Box 165, Folder 10)
    - Federally Unapproved Medications for the Treatment of AIDS and Related Conditions, 1986; 557364 (Reel 143, Box 175, Folder 3)
    - Gay Men's Health Crisis (GMHC). Annual Report, 1988/1989; 557365 (Reel 136, Box 165, Folder 12)
    - Glossary of ACT UP Related Acronyms, n.d.; 557366 (Reel 144, Box 175, Folder 5)
    - Gordon, David K., and Robert F. Kennedy, Jr. The Legend of City Water: Recommendations for Rescuing the New York City Water Supply, 1991; 557367 (Reel 136, Box 165, Folder 13)
    - Grinspoon, Lester, MD. AIDS, Marijuana, and Human Rights, 1994; 557368 (Reel 136, Box 165, Folder 14)
    - Guinan, Mary E. AIDS and Women in the United States, circa 1987; 557369 (Reel 136, Box 165, Folder 15)
    - Health Education AIDS Liaison (HEAL), 1990; 557370; Various articles and reports (Reel 136, Box 165, Folder 16)
    - Hinckley, Tom, and Evan Wilder. Report from the 1993 UCLA/UCI AIDS Symposium, 557371 (Reel 136, Box 166, Folder 1)
    - HIV Treatment Evaluation, 1988; 557372; Draft (Reel 136, Box 166, Folder 2)
    - How Single-Payer Is Financed, 1993; 557373 (Reel 136, Box 165, Folder 11)
    - The Intergovernmental Health Policy Project at George Washington University. Profiles of State-Level Health Care Reform Laws, 1993; 557374 (Reel 136, Box 166, Folder 4)
    - Interleukin 2, Inc. Annual Report, 1985; 557375 (Reel 137, Box 166, Folder 5)
    - Leitman, Paul, MD. TAT Inhibitor., 1992; 557376 (Reel 137, Box 166, Folder 7)
    - Lesbian and Gay Directory of Services: New York Metropolitan Area, 1990; 557377 (Reel 137, Box 166, Folder 8)
    - Long, Iris, n.d.; 557378; Various reports (Reel 137, Box 166, Folder 9)
    - Mann, Jonathan, 1991; 557379; Materials regarding AIDS (Reel 137, Box 166, Folder 10)
    - Medical reports, n.d.; 557380; Assorted (Reel 144, Box 175, Folder 7-10)
    - Medley, Raan. AIDS Trial Balloon., n.d.; 557381 (Reel 137, Box 166, Folder 11)
    - Midwest Academy. Citizens Action Health Care Strategy Meeting., 1993; 557382 (Reel 137, Box 166, Folder 12)
    - National AIDS Information Clearinghouse (NAIC). Media kit, n.d.; 557383 (Reel 137, Box 167, Folder 1)
    - The National Association of People with AIDS. A Profile of the Challenges Facing Americans Living with HIV., 1992; 557384 (Reel 137, Box 166, Folder 13)
    - National Cancer Institute and National Institute of Allergy and Infectious Diseases, National Institutes of Health. AIDS Diagnosis and Treatment., 1985; 557385 (Reel 137, Box 166, Folder 14)
    - National Coalition for the Homeless, 557386
      - AIDS and Homelessness: A Growing Concern., 1989; 557387 (Reel 137, Box 166, Folder 16)
      - Fighting to Live: Homeless People with AIDS., circa 1991; 557388 (Reel 137, Box 166, Folder 15)
    - National Commission on AIDS. America Living with AIDS., 1990; 557389 (Reel 137, Box 166, Folder 17)
    - National Conference on HIV Infection and AIDS among Racial and Ethnic Populations. Panel Presentation on Homelessness and AIDS, 1989; 557390; Transcript (Reel 136, Box 166, Folder 3)
    - National Institute of Allergy and Infectious Diseases, 557391
      - AIDS Clinical Trials Group (ACTG), 557392
        - ICM [Institute of Clinical Medicine] 1505/ACTG 127, 1990; 557393 (Reel 138, Box 167, Folder 9)
        - Protocol ACTG 135, Version 2.0, 1991; 557394 (Reel 137, Box 167, Folder 2)
        - Amended Protocol ACTG 142, Version 2.0, 1990; 557395 (Reel 138, Box 167, Folder 10)
        - Protocol ACTG 150, Version 2.0, 1991; 557396 (Reel 137, Box 167, Folder 3)
        - Final version ACTG 154, Version 2.0, 1991 Apr 4; 557397 (Reel 137, Box 167, Folder 4)
        - Protocol ACTG 172, Version 2.0, 1991; 557398 (Reel 137, Box 167, Folder 5)
        - Protocol ACTG 174, Version 1.0, 1991; 557399 (Reel 138, Box 167, Folder 6)
      - AIDS Program: AIDS/HIV Related Research, 1989; 557400 (Reel 138, Box 167, Folder 8)
      - Various materials, n.d.; 557401 (Reel 138, Box 167, Folder 7)
      - Volume II, n.d.; 557402 (Reel 138, Box 167, Folder 11)
    - National Institutes of Health AIDS Executive Committee. Future Directions for AIDS Research: Report to Congress from the Ad Hoc Consultants to the National Institutes of Health AIDS Committee., 1986 Nov; 557403 (Reel 138, Box 168, Folder 1)
    - Nemer, Kirk D. The Potential Liability of Insurance Companies and Self-Insured Businesses for Unauthorized Disclosure of Medical Information Provided in Connection with AIDS Related Insurance Claims. [Washington, DC]: Congressional Research Service, Libra, 1988; 557404 (Reel 138, Box 168, Folder 2)
    - New Drugs in the United States: An FDA Consumer Special Report. Rev. ed., 1990; 557405; Last article is missing. Includes Frank Young's "The Reality Behind the Headlines."; Photocopy (Reel 143, Box 175, Folder 1)
    - New Jersey Pediatric AIDS Advisory Committee. Generations in Jeopardy, 1989; 557406 (Reel 138, Box 168, Folder 3)
    - New York City, 557407
      - Commission on Human Rights, 557408
        - AIDS and People of Color: The Discrimination Impact, 1986; 557409 (Reel 138, Box 168, Folder 5)
        - Report on Discrimination against People with AIDS, 1983 Nov-1986 Apr; 557410 (Reel 138, Box 168, Folder 4)
      - Department of Health, 557411
        - AIDS: A Resource Guide for New York City, 1989; 557412 (Reel 139, Box 169, Folder 2)
        - AIDS Surveillance Unit. Update., 557413
          - 1988, 557414 (Reel 138, Box 168, Folder 6)
          - 1989, 557415 (Reel 138, Box 168, Folder 8)
          - 1990-1991, 557416 (Reel 138, Box 168, Folder 9)
        - Guidelines for Physicians on HIV Counseling and Testing and Related Documents, 1989; 557417 (Reel 139, Box 169, Folder 1)
        - HIV Infection, n.d.; 557418 (Reel 138, Box 168, Folder 7)
        - The Mayor's Management Report, 1993; 557419 (Reel 139, Box 168, Folder 10-12)
        - Pediatric HIV/AIDS Resource Packet #7, 1991 Jul; 557420 (Reel 139, Box 169, Folder 4)
        - Women and HIV/AIDS Resource Packet #4, 1991 Jan; 557421 (Reel 139, Box 169, Folder 3)
      - Interagency Task Force on AIDS. Strategic Plan for AIDS, 1988 May; 557422 (Reel 139, Box 169, Folder 5)
    - New York State, 557423
      - AIDS: New York's Response, a Five-Year Interagency Plan, 1989; 557424 (Reel 141, Box 171, Folder 3)
      - AIDS Advisory Council, 1994; 557425 (Reel 141, Box 171, Folder 4)
      - AIDS/HIV Clinical Trials, 557426
        - Vol. 2, no. 2, 1992; 557427 (Reel 139, Box 169, Folder 6)
        - Vol. 2, no. 2 and 3, 1992; 557428 (Reel 140, Box 169, Folder 7)
      - Department of Health, 557429
        - AIDS, 1985; 557430 (Reel 141, Box 171, Folder 1)
        - AIDS Institute Presents the Fourth Annual Statewide HIV/AIDS Policy Conference, 1993 Nov; 557431 (Reel 140, Box 170, Folder 7)
        - CD4, 1994; 557432 (Reel 141, Box 171, Folder 2)
      - Directory of AIDS/HIV Clinical Trials, 1993-1995; 557433 (Reel 140, Box 170, Folder 1-6)
      - A Physician's Guide to AIDS: Issues in the Medical Office, 1988; 557434 (Reel 141, Box 171, Folder 5)
    - NOVA Research Company, and National AIDS Demonstration Research Project (U.S.). Women and AIDS: An Annotated Bibliography for Project Staff and Clients. 4th ed. Bethesda, Maryland: NOVA Research Company, 1989; 557435 (Reel 141, Box 171, Folder 6)
    - Office of Technology Assessment. The Costs of AIDS and Other HIV Infections: Review of the Estimates, 1987; 557436; The Office of Technology Assessment was a scientific advisory office of the U.S. Congress from 1972-1995. (Reel 141, Box 171, Folder 7)
    - Overton, Sara. Report to ACT UP Regarding Delta Airlines, n.d.; 557437 (Reel 141, Box 171, Folder 8)
    - Pan American Health Organization. The Expanded Program on Immunization (EPI): Poliomyelitis in the Americas and Its Eradication by 1990. Washington, D.C.: Organizacion Panamericana de la Salud, Oficina Sanitaria Panamericana, Oficina Regional de la Organi, 1984; 557438 (Reel 141, Box 171, Folder 9)
    - Panos Institute. AIDS and the Third World, 1986; 557439 (Reel 141, Box 171, Folder 10)
    - Pediatric AIDS Coalition. Pediatric AIDS Coalition: 1991 Legislative Agenda, circa 1991; 557440 (Reel 141, Box 171, Folder 11)
    - Pfizer Pharmaceuticals. Psychotherapeutic Agents: Programmed Instructions, n.d.; 557441 (Reel 141, Box 171, Folder 14)
    - Prevention of Human Immunodeficiency Virus (HIV) Infection among Ethnic/Racial Minority Populations in the United States, 1987 Aug 5; 557442; Draft (Reel 144, Box 175, Folder 4)
    - Project Inform. Report of Its Survey of AIDS/ARC Patients Self-medicating Treatments Imported from Mexico, 1987; 557443 (Reel 141, Box 171, Folder 12)
    - Public Agenda Foundation. Sex on Campus: Sexually Transmitted Disease, 1980; 557444 (Reel 141, Box 171, Folder 13)
    - Roberts, Richard, MD. Ribavirin Delays Progression of the Lymphadenopathy Syndrome to the Acquired Immunodeficiency Syndrome, 1987; 557445; Presentation transcript (Reel 141, Box 171, Folder 15)
    - Rochon, James. A New Clinical Trials Design for AIDS Research: The Measured-choice Design. University of Western Ontario, n.d.; 557446 (Reel 141, Box 172, Folder 1)
    - Rubenfeld, Abby R., ed. AIDS Legal Guide. 2nd ed. New York: Lambda Legal Defense and Education Fund, Inc., 1987; 557447 (Reel 137, Box 166, Folder 6)
    - Sinclair, Lister. What Causes AIDS? A Second Look. The Canadian Broadcasting Corporation, 1992; 557448; This article is reproduced in Sinclair's book Ideas Transcripts. Fall 1991. (Reel 141, Box 172, Folder 3)
    - Site reports, core committee members, and organizational charts], 1991 Apr, Jun-Jul; 557449 (Reel 144, Box 175, Folder 6)
    - Slutsky, Sonia. The Walls Speak: Images of Reproductive Rights in American Political Protest Poster Artwork of the 1980s and the Early 1990s. Senior thesis, Vassar College, 1994; 557450 (Reel 141, Box 172, Folder 4)
    - Smith, Jerry L. America's Crisis Situation: AIDS via Fiat Money, 1991; 557451 (Reel 142, Box 172, Folder 5)
    - Des Spécialistes répondent à vos questions: SIDA: la maladie, la transmission, les risques, les précautions, les espoirs: l'information au public, arme principale de la lutte. Paris: Fondation internationale pour l'information scientifique, 1985; 557452; Sous la direction du Pr. Luc Montagnier, Institut Pasteur. (Reel 141, Box 172, Folder 2)
    - Stricker, Raphael B., n.d.; 557453; Various reports (Reel 142, Box 172, Folder 6)
    - Swarz, Jeffery R., and Frederic Greenberg. Investment Research: AIDS, 1988; 557454 (Reel 142, Box 172, Folder 7)
    - Tilly, Charles. Selected Readings on Political Change: 1990 Version. Working paper series. New York: Center for Studies of Social Change, New School for Social Research, 557455 (Reel 142, Box 172, Folder 8)
    - United Nations. Manual on Human Rights Reporting, 1991; 557456 (Reel 142, Box 172, Folder 10)
    - United States, 557457
      - AIDS Drugs: Where Are They?: Seventy-Third Report. Washington: U.S. G.P.O., 1988, and The Federal Response to AIDS: Twenty-ninth Report. Washington: U.S. G.P.O., 1983; 557458 (Reel 142, Box 172, Folder 12)
      - Agency for International Development. HIV Infection and AIDS, 1989; 557459 (Reel 142, Box 172, Folder 11)
      - Department of Health and Human Services, 557460
        - Centers for Disease Control, 557461
          - Acquired Immunodeficiency Syndrome, AIDS: Recommendations and Guidelines, November 1982-November 1986. Atlanta: Centers for Disease Control, Public Health Service, Dept. of Health and Human Services, 1987; 557462 (Reel 142, Box 173, Folder 2)
          - A Guide to Selected HIV- and AIDS-Related Information Services in the United States. Rockville, MD: CDC National AIDS Clearinghouse, 1993; 557463 (Reel 142, Box 172, Folder 14)
          - 1992 Revised Classification System for HIV Infection and Expanded AIDS Surveillance Case Definition for Adolescents and Adults. Atlanta: U.S. Dept. of Health and Human Services, Public Health Service, Centers for Disease Control, 1991; 557464; Draft (Reel 142, Box 173, Folder 1)
          - Reports on HIV/AIDS 1991. Atlanta: Dept. of Health & Human Services, Public Health Service, Centers for Disease Control, 1992; 557465; Compilation of Morbidity and Mortality Weekly Report articles from 1991. (Reel 142, Box 172, Folder 13)
      - Department of Veterans Affairs, 557466
        - Annual Report, 1991; 557467 (Reel 143, Box 173, Folder 9)
        - Federal Benefits for Veterans and Dependents, 1992; 557468 (Reel 143, Box 173, Folder 8)
        - VA Today, n.d.; 557469 (Reel 143, Box 173, Folder 7)
      - The Drug Manufacturing Industry: A Prescription for Profits: Staff Report of the Special Committee on Aging, United States Senate. S. prt, 102-50. Washington: U.S. G.P.O., 1991; 557470 (Reel 142, Box 173, Folder 6)
      - Government Accountability Office, 557471
        - Medicaid Long-term Care, 1994; 557472 (Reel 142, Box 173, Folder 5)
        - Reports on Health, Education, Employment and Training, and Income Security, 1993; 557473 (Reel 142, Box 173, Folder 4)
      - National Institute of Health. AIDS Review, 1992; 557474 (Reel 142, Box 173, Folder 3)
      - Working Group, 557475
        - Draft of President Clinton's healthcare policy, n.d.; 557476 (Reel 143, Box 173, Folder 10)
    - Wilder, Evan. AIDS 2.02, 1993; 557477 (Reel 143, Box 173, Folder 11)
    - Wolfe, Maxine, et al., 557478
      - What's Wrong with the Federal Drug Administration, 1993; 557479 (Reel 143, Box 173, Folder 12)
      - Who Makes National Health Care Policy: The Government of Burroughs Wellcome?, 1993; 557480 (Reel 143, Box 173, Folder 13)
    - World Health Organization, 557481
      - Directory of Nongovernmental Organizations in Official Relations with the World Health Organization, 1987; 557482 (Reel 143, Box 173, Folder 14)
      - Guide to Planning AIDS Health Care Promotion, n.d.; 557483; Draft (Reel 142, Box 172, Folder 9)
      - Safe Blood and Blood Products. Introductory Module: Guidelines and Principles for Safe Blood Transfusion Practice, 557484; Not microfilmed (Box 174, Folder 2)
      - Safe Blood and Blood Products. Module 1: Safe Blood Donation, 557485; Not microfilmed (Box 174, Folder 3)
      - Safe Blood and Blood Products. Module 2: Screening for HIV and Other Infectious Agents, 557486; Not microfilmed (Box 174, Folder 4)
      - Safe Blood and Blood Products. Module 3: Blood Group Serology, 557487; Not microfilmed (Box 174, Folder 5)
      - Safe Blood and Blood Products. Trainer's Guide, 557488; Not microfilmed (Box 174, Folder 6)
      - Various reports, n.d.; 557489 (Reel 143, Box 174, Folder 1)
    - Young, Frank E. Remarks at the Second International Lesbian and Gay Health Conference and AIDS Forum. Boston, 1988; 557490 (Reel 143, Box 175, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous pamphlets, 557491
      - AIDS Hotline: Important Information Statement, n.d.; 557492 (Reel 145, Box 177, Folder 1)
      - APLA Manual del Cliente, n.d.; 557493 (Reel 145, Box 177, Folder 2)
      - Burroughs Wellcome Company. What You Need to Know about STDs, n.d.; 557494 (Reel 145, Box 177, Folder 3)
      - Carter, George M. ACT UP, the AIDS War and Activism. Pamphlet 15. Open Magazine pamphlet series, 1992 Jan; 557495 (Reel 145, Box 177, Folder 4)
      - Estate Project for Artists with AIDS. Future Safe: The Present is the Future, 1992; 557496 (Reel 145, Box 177, Folder 6)
      - Federal Republic of Germany. Support Programmes on AIDS for Developing Countries, 1993; 557497 (Reel 145, Box 177, Folder 7)
      - François-Xavier Bagnoud (FXB), n.d.; 557498 (Reel 145, Box 177, Folder 5)
      - Gay Men's Health Crisis (GMHC), n.d.; 557499 (Reel 145, Box 177, Folder 8)
      - Hafer, Dick. AIDS Is Looking for You., n.d.; 557500 (Reel 145, Box 177, Folder 9)
      - Haitian Coalition on AIDS, n.d.; 557501 (Reel 145, Box 177, Folder 10)
      - Health, Education, Resource Organization. AIDS., n.d.; 557502 (Reel 145, Box 177, Folder 12)
      - Health pamphlets, n.d.; 557503 (Reel 145, Box 177, Folder 13)
      - Hetrick-Martin Institute Incorporated. Tales of the Closet., n.d.; 557504 (Reel 145, Box 177, Folder 11)
      - Himalayan Institute of New York, n.d.; 557505 (Reel 145, Box 177, Folder 14)
      - International AIDS Handbook for Journalists, 557506 (Reel 145, Box 177, Folder 15)
      - Lambda. Living with AIDS., n.d.; 557507 (Reel 145, Box 177, Folder 16)
      - National AIDS Clearinghouse, 1991; 557508 (Reel 145, Box 177, Folder 17)
      - National AIDS Information Clearinghouse. Users Guide., n.d.; 557509 (Reel 145, Box 177, Folder 19)
      - National Center for Health Education, n.d.; 557510 (Reel 145, Box 177, Folder 18)
      - New York Academy of Medicine. AIDS, vol. 437, n.d.; 557511 (Reel 145, Box 177, Folder 20)
      - New York City, 557512
        - Department of Health. The AIDS Training Institute, n.d.; 557513 (Reel 145, Box 177, Folder 22)
      - New York State, 557514
        - Department of Health, 557515
          - AIDS Advisory Council. Illusions of Immortality, n.d.; 557516 (Reel 145, Box 177, Folder 24)
          - Angela's Dream, n.d.; 557517 (Reel 145, Box 177, Folder 21)
          - A First Step, n.d.; 557518 (Reel 145, Box 177, Folder 25)
          - Into the '90s, n.d.; 557519 (Reel 145, Box 177, Folder 23)
      - Nutritionists in AIDS Care (NIAC). HIV: Fight Back with Nutrition, 1992; 557520 (Reel 145, Box 177, Folder 26)
      - Pekkanen, John. Are We Closing in on AIDS?, n.d.; 557521 (Reel 145, Box 177, Folder 27)
      - Politics of AIDS Frontline, 1987; 557522 (Reel 145, Box 177, Folder 28)
      - Scottish AIDS Monitor (SAM). HIV, n.d.; 557523 (Reel 145, Box 177, Folder 29)
      - Stuurgroep Aidspreventie Homo's. Safe Sex for Leather Men. Amsterdam, The Netherlands: Stuurgroep Aidspreventie Homo's, 557524 (Reel 145, Box 177, Folder 30)
      - Tsongas, Paul C. A Call to Economic Arms, n.d.; 557525 (Reel 145, Box 177, Folder 31)
      - United States, 557526
        - Catholic Conference. The Many Faces of AIDS, n.d.; 557527 (Reel 145, Box 177, Folder 32)
        - Department of Health. What Are Clinical Trials All About?, n.d.; 557528 (Reel 145, Box 177, Folder 33)
  - X.D. Newsletters and serials, 1982-1995, n.d.; 557529; 14 boxes
    Subseries X.D. Newsletters and serials is arranged alphabetically; it consists of a representative sampling of newsletters from gay and lesbian organizations, serials from medical companies, mainstream periodicals, and miscellaneous newspapers.
    - ACT UP, 557530
      - Chapters, 557531
        - Atlanta, n.d.; 557532 (Reel 146, Box 178, Folder 6)
        - Austin, n.d.; 557533 (Reel 146, Box 178, Folder 7)
        - Boston, n.d.; 557534 (Reel 146, Box 178, Folder 8)
        - Bruxelles, n.d.; 557535 (Reel 146, Box 178, Folder 9)
        - Kansas City, Missouri, n.d.; 557536 (Reel 146, Box 178, Folder 11)
        - London, 557537 (Reel 146, Box 178, Folder 13)
        - Los Angeles, n.d.; 557538 (Reel 146, Box 178, Folder 12)
        - New York, 557539
          - Digest, 1990-1991, 1993-1994; 557540 (Reel 146, Box 178, Folder 2-4)
          - Newsletter, n.d.; 557541 (Reel 146, Box 178, Folder 1)
        - Orange County, California, n.d.; 557542 (Reel 146, Box 178, Folder 14)
        - Paris, n.d.; 557543 (Reel 146, Box 178, Folder 14)
        - Philadelphia, n.d.; 557544 (Reel 146, Box 178, Folder 16)
        - Pittsburgh, n.d.; 557545 (Reel 146, Box 178, Folder 15)
        - Portland, 557546 (Reel 146, Box 178, Folder 17)
        - San Francisco, n.d.; 557547 (Reel 146, Box 178, Folder 18)
        - Seattle, n.d.; 557548 (Reel 146, Box 178, Folder 19)
        - Sydney, n.d.; 557549 (Reel 146, Box 178, Folder 20)
        - Washington, DC, 557550 (Reel 146, Box 178, Folder 10)
      - Just Kids. Street Sheet, n.d.; 557551 (Reel 146, Box 178, Folder 5)
      - Reports, 1989-1991; 557552 (Reel 147, Box 179, Folder 1-3)
      - Tell It to ACT UP (TITA), 1990-1992; 557553 (Reel 147, Box 179, Folder 4-6)
    - Action Alert, New York City, 1990; 557554 (Reel 147, Box 180, Folder 19)
    - Action SIDA, Toronto, Ontario, 1989; 557555 (Reel 147, Box 180, Folder 20)
    - The Advocate, Los Angeles, California, 1988, 1990; 557556; Not microfilmed (Box 180, Folder 21)
    - Aid for AIDS of Nevada (AFAN), 1991; 557557 (Reel 147, Box 180, Folder 1)
    - AIDS Action, London, England, 1990, 1992; 557558 (Reel 147, Box 180, Folder 2)
    - AIDS Captions, Virginia, 1995; 557559 (Reel 147, Box 180, Folder 3)
    - AIDS Center News, Los Angeles, California, 1984; 557560 (Reel 147, Box 180, Folder 4)
    - AIDS Clinical Care, Massachusetts, 1991-1992; 557561 (Reel 147, Box 180, Folder 5)
    - AIDS Educator, San Francisco, California, 1987; 557562 (Reel 147, Box 180, Folder 6)